[Music]
hello everyone this is E on ey censored
Supernatural Bible change on YouTube and
today is a special show where I have
Rony with us she's someone in our in our
community she's been in a community for
a while she'll have to tell us how many
years um and she's going to share her
testimony her Christian testimony how
she be became born again and these are
always wonderful to hear especially from
people in our community who see the
supernatural Bible changes and if you're
not yet aware our bibles are under
satanic Siege and supernaturally
changing and we Proclaim that Jesus is
the Christ the son of God the word of
God according to John 1:1 and
Revelations
1913 but we are steadfast in proclaiming
the truth
that the Bible is under satanic Siege
and supernaturally
changing and we share the Gospel of
Jesus Christ and we share the truth
about the Bible changes but today again
I'm really glad we have rowny with us
and rowny God bless you and thank you
for um taking the time out of your
schedule to share what Jesus Christ has
done in your life so I'm just going to
go ahead and give you the rign
and um and looking forward to learning
more about you in this hour so please go
ahead Rony and and um introduce yourself
and then start sharing your
testimony hi everyone um my name is
Ronnie and um I'm so glad to be here um
I'm so glad that I have the opportunity
to share this you know kind of funny
that that a has asked for testimonies
because I've been feeling this in my
heart for
a that I needed to
[Music]
share I'm so sorry my testimony because
it's been a long time since I've done it
um but anyway um and I I come the
scripture comes to
mind in Revelations 12:1 and they
overcame him by the blood of the lamb
and by the word of their testimony and
they love not their lives to
death so anyway I hope I can get through
this
um
anyway I started really probably
learning about God when I was really
young in like you know um preschool and
first grade second
grade um and pretty much was raised
Presbyterian and Lutheran um and then we
kind of quit going to church we had
moved away from there from the churches
we had gone to and my first experience
with God was just that he was really big
I knew that he was you know there but um
I just saw him as so far away you know
and just this really huge um being that
I really couldn't really connect with
you know that's sort of my um initial
experience and then as I got older I
just um was really just a wild kid I you
know was with a gang of girls and we I
started smoking and drinking at a very
young age probably like at the age of
fifth grade and later on started you
know taking a few drugs light drugs
um and I think one of the biggest things
that I did that I really didn't like was
I had to lie to my parents so much about
the things that I was doing and I always
remembered that as just I didn't like
that that was a big problem for me but I
had to do it to to do the things that
you know I wanted to do so um anyway
that was kind of my Early Childhood
background had a great mother she was
wonderful my father um he was a good
father he had a drinking problem but he
was you know great supporter and took
really good care of us and we had a lot
of close family ties so I had like an
older brother and
sister but anyway um so that was pretty
much my early experiences with with God
and then um I had started when I got
into high school I started to recognize
that I just wanted to be different I
didn't want to drink and smoke and party
anymore so I kind of found a new set of
friends and started getting more into
health and fitness and just taking care
of myself more and then in
1981 I do remember this day distinctly I
was on the school lawn at high school
and one of my friends had just gotten
saved and fact I think she was smoking a
cigarette I mean she had just gotten
saved and she told me about Jesus and
then he wanted to save me and I accepted
him you know with her testimony and what
she told me about him and um that was
when he completely changed my life um I
do remember and this is a funny thing
you know because I am a Biblical
cosmologist I believe that you know we
live in an enclosed structure and a flat
plane but I remember looking up to the
heavens and I remember God Jesus the
Holy Spirit whoever speaking to me and
saying I am right here you know I'm not
millions of miles away I am right
here and so I always remembered that you
know that was like oh wow he's not far
away he's right here so that was I did
my 180 you know I completely turned from
all my sins I became a completely God
just completely changed me which is
what's so wonderful about salvation
right I mean sometimes we fall back into
our patterns but he's so great you know
he can really turn us
around so anyway I remember the relief
about not having to lie anymore you know
that was such when I repented it was
just such a relief such a relief I was
not a liar anymore you know I didn't
want to be one I wanted to tell the
truth um so then after that I kind of
started searching around um for
different churches gone to Baptist
Church um my family wasn't going to
church so I kind of just did this on my
own and then I finally caught up with a
Holiness um congregation that um you
know they're very very strict you know
we didn't we didn't go to movies we
didn't wear jewelry wear makeup it was
um very much a holiest
congregation and I do remember that the
pastor and his family they had four kids
and they were they just loved me into
the fold I mean literally just I you
know when I'd miss they'd call me back
and say hey you're going to come to
church again and you know so was that
kind of thing in fact I didn't drive
until I got married so I would even have
one of the daughters would come and pick
me up to get me there so it kind of kept
me on track which was really nice but
anyway that was my first experience
really uh with the King James Bible
because that was the only version they
used and so when I joined this church
and became a member in the early 880s
that's the only Bible I used you know I
had uh I've had the same one since then
and it was I think copyrighted in 1966
so um you know at that point once I got
saved and I joined this church pretty
much started going to every single event
you know we went to um Church camp and
you know all of their meetings and you
know Sunday and Wednesday and and all
that sort of things so I really studied
the word I heard the word a lot you know
it was preached a lot so I was there
listening and studying it on my
own um but anyway and then about you
know a year after that um the my first
husband he had just gotten saved
recently and so he kind of grew up the
same way that I grew up and so we um
started dating and then I got married
pretty young at 18
and he felt called to preach so um it's
just kind of funny how this church did
things um so we got sent out to preach
at a
church um about three hours away from
where we lived and this is in Casper
Wyoming Minds you um snow you know ice
that sort of things but for like a year
and a half we drove like the three hours
uh to the church on Sunday and then um I
think nobody really had a vehicle we had
like five members and we had a bunch of
kids and so I taught children's church
in Sunday school but um we would pick
them all up and bring them to church and
then we'd you know take them all home
and then we'd head back to to where we
lived um and then probably we moved up
there like in a year and a half we moved
to the church and we just stayed there
and I remember we just did everything we
fixed holes in the floors we fixed the
roof you know we just were in it we were
just doing whatever we needed to do so
um and then we felt you know because we
H were so we really weren't raised in
the church or in a Christian environment
so we both felt the need to learn more
you know and be more instructed by
Elders so we ended up going to South
Dakota and uh to a larger church and we
were youth pastors there for a while and
then we got appointed to another church
which was another place in South Dakota
and pastor that for a couple years um I
think it had 200 people in the town it
was on an Indian Reservation so it was a
very interesting experience but we had
some really good times with the folks
that we you know we pastored but anyway
that was my um beginning experience you
know um with the Bible with KJV with
knowing god and that sort of thing and
of course along the way you know I'm
preaching to different people um even in
school when I got saved and my parents
parents and you know everybody else I
could tell about Jesus I was telling
everybody um but anyway um we ended up
moving to
Tennessee um because again we wanted to
get more educated I don't know that
that's always a good thing but so we
came there was a church school in
Cleveland Tennessee so we moved here for
my husband to go to school and he was
going to just go to the into the
ministerial program but ended up later I
think going into computers and
accounting
and then I ended up going to school um
becoming a physical
therapist um so anyway we moved from
South Dakota to Tennessee and which is
where I'm at now and have stayed here um
kind of along the
journey um
we I guess we got into school and so we
couldn't really go to church as much and
the churches were much different in
Tennessee than they were in um Casper I
mean
it was this I mean this is kind of
considered the Bible Belt but I felt
like they were much looser I mean they
allowed a lot more than what we were
kind of used to so you know we kind of
got into that environment um anyway um
we sort of fell away from the Lord from
there because we got really into our
education and um different things I mean
we still went to church a little bit but
we weren't as you know into it as we
were before we weren't as committed um
so so uh so we eventually ended up in a
divorce um 2000 I guess is when we got
divorced and so pretty much I was kind
of doing my own thing I was you know
practicing physical therapy and I I
still love I still believed in God I
just wasn't committed in serving him
because I couldn't really find a church
here that I really enjoyed going to it
was it was a struggle um from the ones
I'd come from
before and um so
then my B my second big Awakening was in
2017 I had to have a knee surgery and
I'm you know just realizing what YouTube
was so I'm you know laying there icing
my knee doing my exercises looking up at
YouTube and up Pops the Flat Earth stuff
and I was like whoa you know what's that
and um you know honestly all I had to do
was look at Genesis 1 and started
reading some of the scriptures and I
knew it was real I mean I knew because I
I W remember walking outside of my home
and this was right when I'd watched the
videos it didn't take much to convince
me I looked outside and I said nothing
is moving I mean it's it's still and so
that was an epiphany for me and I do
remember when I first got
saved looking up and God spoke to me
again he said I told you I was right
here you know and it's so amazing how
God works you know he sees us from the
beginning to the end and you know he
brings those things to our remembrance
which is really wonderful so that kind
of honestly finding out about the Flat
Earth got me back on the track of
wanting to serve the Lord again and to
really get committed although again it
was really hard to
find you know a church um in fact it
still
is but um I just began to study the word
on my own and then you know of course
you come across people like Rob skeba
and the Nephilim and you know you go
down that pathway and you're just like
in awe because you never heard these
things in your life I mean you know in
churches that I was in you know you just
didn't hear about this stuff so you know
I kind of consumed everything I could
consume you know went and read you know
my Bible again read um J The Book of
jasher Enoch you know the book of
jubilees and and all those extra
biblical texts which I found really
interesting but then um so anyway I was
you know then we of course we ran into
covid or excuse me I guess we're not
supposed to say that but um that was
kind of a rough time I think for
everyone
um but let's see probably I'm trying to
think probably in 2019 was when I heard
about the Bible changes and the Mandela
effect and it came I came along ey's
Channel and um cat's Channel and um you
know started really hearing more about
it then and honestly it didn't take me
long i i w you know that's why I'm
always so shocked with that people can
hear and and know the Bible and not be
shocked that it's changed not see that
it's been changed um because I I think
it I can't remember exact the exact um
address but it was in James I think it
was the first chapter where it says Be
You a doer of the of the word and not a
hearer only but now it says work that
was one of my favorite scriptures I was
like there was no way it doesn't even
make sense to be a doer of the work it's
a doer of the word you know not a hearer
only so um that one and of course you
know um The Lord's Prayer because I was
initially raised in b or excuse me in a
presbyterian and Lutheran Church one of
the things I did notice we always had to
quote the Lord's Prayer and it was
always debtors in that church they had
it written on paper and when I became a
Christian and I started reading my own
Bible I noticed well oh this is
interesting the king J the KJV says
trespasses you know so I noticed that
difference so when this came up you know
that wasn't hard for me to jump off and
I always remember like noi when I you
know started reading the Bible again in
2017 you know in Matthew when it talked
about as in the days of Noah and it said
Noy I kept thinking that just that just
doesn't sound right you know like did I
not recognize that it said Noy before um
but of course when I found out that
things were changing
um you know I realized that was a change
but um anyway that's kind of where I'm
at now I'm sort of with y'all I I'm kind
of off in the I don't feel like I am
able to get on as much to talk to
everybody I appreciate all your
testimonies and when you guys get on and
share your stuff it it it's a real
blessing to me so so um I appreciate all
that like I said I'm not always able to
get on in the chat and catch the live
streams and such but um anyway um I've
told several I mean like I said I this
is kind of the Bible Belt and on the
management team that I'm on I'm GNA say
there's probably 25 of us and I would
say 99% would profess to be uh a
Christian and serving God so I have told
several people here and it just blows my
mind you know um they all agree that
yeah this is what it said this is what
it said this is what it said but then
they'll completely get that glazed
Overlook you know like oh okay I'll see
you later and then the subject never
comes up again but you know I keep
trying there is one girl in my office I
just love her to death she um when I
came upon the Flat Earth I shared it
with her and she believed believes it
and then when the Mandela changes I
shared it with her and she believes it
and she's a wonderful Christian woman so
I feel kind of blessed because I do have
someone in my world that I can share
this with um and we just share it all
you know we talk a lot about stuff and
my husband my husband now honestly um
he he sees it all you know so um I feel
super blessed to have at least two
people in my life you know that um that
see the changes because I hear people
talk all the time and my heart just goes
out to them that there's just nobody
they can talk to about it and um wow you
know that'd be hard so um anyway um my
my last thing I did want to
share is I've been having some issues I
had some issues over the last year I've
never had any health issues really my
entire life I've been pretty healthy but
I had passed out a year ago and had some
seizures and um they kind of continued
on um they checked me out for everything
they couldn't find anything wrong um
checked my brain checked my heart you
know pretty much went through the whole
gamut of doctors um so anyway um the
pray prayer group had prayed for me back
in March and um I feel like I've been
healed I haven't had any since then so
thank you guys so much for praying for
me and just for praying for the
community because we all need each other
we all need each other's prayers we need
each other's support you know even
though we're in different places but
anyway I just wanted to tell y'all thank
you for um being such a blessing to me
um and the prophecy that um Christine I
believe gave wow I mean just wow thank
you Jesus thank you God I mean that was
just powerful powerful unbelievable well
yeah I had to listen to it several times
praise the Lord that's why I actually
put it up on my Channel I want to ask
you Ronnie yeah I want to go back
because you you shared quite a bit of
your journey with Jesus I want to go
back to when you were you said that you
were in Ministry that you involved in in
what capacity were you involved in
Ministry you and your first
husband well um he was a p he was a
preacher so um you know it's funny they
just
in it's church God a prophecy but they
would they send you out if you think
you're called to preach they'll just
send you to a church you know if they
feel led of the Lord they'll send you
out so um we pastored a couple little
small churches one was in Wyoming one
was in um South Dakota and um we had you
were pastor's wife essentially yeah yes
yes I was and I you know we didn't have
a lot of people so I taught Sunday
school I taught children's church you
know I had to sing specials we pretty
much did it all so we did how many years
did you do that um let's see we moved
here in 1989 so it was
probably I want to say maybe six six or
seven years and then you moved to
Tennessee but where why is it that you
why do you think that you and your
husband became complacent in your faith
you know I think honestly and I hate to
believe it on on people but Tennessee is
this is like the B this was the the
headquarters of the church that we
belong to and it just they're just so
different you know like the people in I
mean if you were saved in Wyoming you
were committed but here it was just a
lot looser I can tell you one thing I'm
G tell you one thing this so that we
join we went to one of the churches here
when we moved to Tennessee and we were
in school right we were going to school
so we weren't ministering anymore but we
you know we still attended um it this
was probably one of the biggest churches
we'd been to there were probably seven
or eight couples about our age we were
in our early
20s and um the pastor was getting a
degree in
Psychology and he was writing a book
about snake handling I don't know why
that was one of his projects in school
but so he was going to these different
churches because there are some around
in the outskirts around here in the
South you know and he was going to some
of these churches well let me just tell
you I don't know I think it was a spirit
that got just leashed in the church
because there were probably seven or
eight couples that were divorced in that
group that we kind of hung out in so I I
don't know you know we just fell away we
started getting into our own thing you
know getting into school we were
disillusioned because we thought we were
going to come here and get educated he
thought he was going to get educated by
and be a better Minister but it just I
don't know we kind of got discouraged I
think um it interesting but that's
that's kind of how that um came about
now my second husband um let me ask you
though so so then you you walked away
from the the church and mind you when
you say walked away do you think that
your were you was your prayer
life non-existent at that point it
wasn't good I mean I believed in the
Bible and every once in a while I'd look
read it do you know what I mean but I
would um yeah I probably felt guilty
because I was kind of doing my own thing
so um I just tried to ignore it and then
how many years so that was in N late
1980s is that
correct and then you say you you kind of
Harden your heart or you you away in
your heart until what
year 2017 so it was so you you walked
away from the Lord for almost 30 years
well let's see I it was probably more
like in 1990 1992 so what would that be
25 years 25 yeah yeah we got to address
this okay go
ahead how was that for you in those 25
years um well I mean you know I was just
kind of doing my own thing I was not
thinking about God you know I um like I
said have any of your old any of your
old friends come alongside you to to
challenge you or to exhort you to
encourage you to to to to Restoration
with the
Lord no not really because a lot of them
fell away like I said the group the
church that we went to there were seven
or eight all of them got divorced it was
very strange
um so not really because I dis it was
the church I was going to I kind of then
just disassociated myself with it and we
were in school and we were working um we
were in school during the week and on
the weekends we were working uh I worked
at a group home for uh adults with um
intellectual disabilities which is where
I work now strangely enough you let me
ask you so you do you think
that I find that amazing so when you
came back to the Lord in
2017 can you tell us that experience of
when you rededicated your life to the
lord well like for you well like I said
it was when I saw that the Earth was
flat yes it it just turned me about and
when I heard about the Nephilim I was
just like hungry to know about these
things that I didn't know about you know
it was like you at this time you you
were now married to your second husband
correct yes and I'll tell you his like
when I first met him I thought he was
crazy because he started talking about
911 and that was my first my he kind of
he's always been like like that sort of
in the sense that you know he didn't
believe everything and so I thought it
was crazy until I started looking at it
myself so that I think allowed me to see
other things you know what I'm saying
like I completely understand and then
did you and your first husband have any
children together we didn't we were
never able to have children what about
your your current husband no we I've
just never been able to so and then as
your are you in contact with your first
husband you know the only thing I did
one time because he got married again
too and I did send him a text because
when I heard about the Nephilim since he
was my preacher you know he was my
spiritual leader yes I sent him a text
and I said did you know about the
you know and he just sent me a text and
said you know I'm just trying to love
people and that one of the things that I
think kind of got me hardened a little
bit is my mother died when I was 27 and
I was very close family like she was the
glue that held everybody together but
when we lost her it just kind of fell
apart you know all the relationships and
the family I mean I'm still I still talk
to my brother and sister my nieces and
stuff but um so I I really think I
forgot about that piece but I think that
Earth was flat and then he spoke to me
like he spoke to me on the school lawn
he said I told you I was I kind of
became I think what what you know then I
went to PT school physical therapy
school and then I got into teaching
exercise classes so I mean I got really
into fitness and I was teaching every
you know class you could imagine I've
taught everything and so I enjoyed
teaching I enjoyed sharing my knowledge
of physical therapy in an exercise
format you know safety that so it wasn't
a bad thing it was just it took me away
from you know where we were at where we
were going um you know and you just get
into other things and like I said I was
think I was holding that deep hurt in my
heart and because I couldn't find a
church here that I felt was the same as
the one I had found before you know and
honestly I haven't really gone to church
even since I got recommitted to God I
started reading everything I you know I
started read I read my Bible again um so
I don't know what kind of changes were
but the point that I'd like to make is
that I had the same Bible since 1981
so I could see you know the same exact
Bible I had everything I have everything
highlighted and you know it's got my
name on it and everything so you know it
wasn't hard for me because and the way
that the Holy Spirit brings the
remembrance of these scriptures back to
your mind I'm I'm in shock sometimes
because you think you wouldn't normally
remember that and all of a sudden
somebody was start talking about and it
comes right into my head like the Holy
Spirit brings it to me and I can quote
it you know a lot of times I can't do
that if on on demand but when the Holy
Spirit does that and then you quote it
and you know it comes out just in such a
you know you remember it you remember
this is what it was now you can't do
that on everything because not all of it
was hidden in your heart you know but a
lot of it you know if you grew up like I
said I I we studied for you know for
seven years my husband was a pastor so
you know I taught children's church I
taught scripture I you know as best I
could um so it wasn't hard and like I
said we really haven't locked into a
community I have this gal at work that
I've told her everything when I when I
see something I tell her and she's just
she's a great Christian lady she does
she is on board she sees it she she can
see it easily just like me so I'm so
grateful for her and then my husband you
know he can see it and we've told you
know he's he's kind of involved in some
political iCal things here not like him
running for office but he's trying to
keep the community um safe if you want
to like like just we're trying he's with
a group that's trying to elect folks
that
um you know that will be
honest and you know block things that
aren't good for the community so he's
got a little group of Christ they're
Christian people but they're they all
believe differently but he's got a
little group that he works with and the
community get some like we just got this
great district attorney elected because
the person there before was just really
crooked so um you know it's in every
Community every community so um we're
just trying you know people that should
be arrested or go to jail don't so he's
kind of heavily involved in that um just
trying to keep the community safe trying
to create community so if they come in
and try
to you know uh do stuff we don't like
you know we have some protection we have
a community we have resources for food
you know eggs and such like we have a
you know a lady and a guy that they have
you know we have cows and we keep it on
their property property so and they have
chickens and so you know that sort of
stuff is are things that he's doing
because he kind of sees the writing on
the wall that things could get really
bad really quick so um anyway yeah
that's what're doing that's what we're
we're doing you know I work full-time so
that keeps me pretty busy and I still
work with the adults with intellectual
intellectual disabilities which I
absolutely love I love these folks they
are one of the funnest and populations
I've ever worked with they're just great
folks
so anyway that's kind of what I'm doing
now we're just trying to pray on our own
we're trying to read scripture best we
can you know sometimes I'll go through
periods where I'll just set the Bible
down I just can't do it you know and
then there's periods when I'm just
trying to filter it and read it because
I just feel so hungry some times you
know just um anyway that's kind of where
things are at with me just hanging on
like everybody else like what else is
gonna happen next you know so I was in
the hospital several times when I had
the seizures and um they give you oh my
goodness all kinds of things to calm me
down Adavan and kepra and anyway it it
affected my memory during those periods
so I don't always remember remember
everything really well from that last
year it's been kind of crazy and I've
always had a really strong memory you
know my old memories are good but like
this last year the things that I did
some of the things are a little bit in
my mind a little bit sketchy so and I
just feel like that was an onslaught
just a spiritual a spiritual attack from
Satan I mean that's how I feel about it
I don't think it
was anything but that so I renounced it
you know re so I appreciate um just
everyone who I just pray that this would
be a blessing to people you know
sometimes you find your life
uninteresting so but you know God has
been telling me when you brought up
these test he's been talking to me about
testifying and I thank you for doing
these testimonies I just really want to
thank you for that I've been needing to
do this and you brought it up and it's
perfect praise the Lord for being
obedient thank you sister okay sister
God bless okay God bless you too bye bye